<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- Created from PDF via Acrobat SaveAsXML -->
<!-- Mapping Table version: 28-February-2003 -->
<TaggedPDF-doc>
<?xpacket begin='﻿' id='W5M0MpCehiHzreSzNTczkc9d'?>
<?xpacket begin="﻿" id="W5M0MpCehiHzreSzNTczkc9d"?>
<x:xmpmeta xmlns:x="adobe:ns:meta/" x:xmptk="Adobe XMP Core 5.4-c005 78.147326, 2012/08/23-13:03:03        ">
   <rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">
      <rdf:Description rdf:about=""
            xmlns:xmp="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/"
            xmlns:xmpMM="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/mm/"
            xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
            xmlns:pdf="http://ns.adobe.com/pdf/1.3/"
            xmlns:xmpRights="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/rights/"
            xmlns:illustrator="http://ns.adobe.com/illustrator/1.0/">
         <xmp:ModifyDate>2014-07-14T00:18:54-07:00</xmp:ModifyDate>
         <xmp:CreateDate>2014-03-28T19:46:09-07:00</xmp:CreateDate>
         <xmp:MetadataDate>2014-07-14T00:18:54-07:00</xmp:MetadataDate>
         <xmpMM:DocumentID>uuid:0546c47e-9271-4da8-b843-42776cd999b0</xmpMM:DocumentID>
         <xmpMM:InstanceID>uuid:33d45d7e-ad33-4674-a791-d3de104f400e</xmpMM:InstanceID>
         <dc:format>xml</dc:format>
         <dc:title>
            <rdf:Alt>
               <rdf:li xml:lang="x-default">2013 Chevron Annual Report</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Alt>
         </dc:title>
         <dc:rights>
            <rdf:Alt>
               <rdf:li xml:lang="x-default">2001 - 2014 Chevron Corporation. All Rights Reserved.&#xA;Retention: cor1120</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Alt>
         </dc:rights>
         <dc:description>
            <rdf:Alt>
               <rdf:li xml:lang="x-default">Chevron Corporation 2013 Annual Report</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Alt>
         </dc:description>
         <dc:creator>
            <rdf:Bag>
               <rdf:li>Chevron Corporation</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Bag>
         </dc:creator>
         <dc:subject>
            <rdf:Bag>
               <rdf:li>2013</rdf:li>
               <rdf:li>Annual Report</rdf:li>
               <rdf:li>Financials</rdf:li>
               <rdf:li>AR</rdf:li>
               <rdf:li>Chevron</rdf:li>
               <rdf:li>Chevron Corporation</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Bag>
         </dc:subject>
         <pdf:Producer>Acrobat Distiller 8.0.0 (Macintosh)</pdf:Producer>
         <pdf:Trapped>Unknown</pdf:Trapped>
         <pdf:Keywords>2013, Annual Report, Financials, AR, Chevron, Chevron Corporation</pdf:Keywords>
         <xmpRights:Marked>True</xmpRights:Marked>
         <illustrator:StartupProfile>Print</illustrator:StartupProfile>
      </rdf:Description>
   </rdf:RDF>
</x:xmpmeta>
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                                                                                                    
                           
<?xpacket end="w"?>
<?xpacket end='r'?>
<bookmark-tree>
<bookmark title="2013 Annual Report Cover">
<destination structID="LinkTarget_841"/>
</bookmark>
</bookmark-tree>
<Part>
<H1 id="LinkTarget_844">To Our Stockholders 
</H1>

<P>Chevron delivered solid financial and operating results in 2013 while advancing our industry-leading queue of major capital projects. Our sound financial performance was reflected in net income of $21.4 billion on sales and other operating revenues of $220 billion. We achieved a competitive </P>

<Sect>
<H4>13.5 percent return on capital employed. And for the 26th consecutive year, we increased our annual dividend payout to stockholders. Our total stockholder returns of just under 15 percent over the past five- and 10-year periods continue to lead our peer group. </H4>

<P>Throughout 2013 our major businesses generated strong operating results. In the upstream, we ranked No. 1 in earnings per barrel relative to our peers for the fourth continuous year. We began production at the Angola liquefied natural gas (LNG) plant and achieved first oil from the Papa Terra project offshore Brazil. In 2013 we also advanced our two world class LNG projects in Western Australia. Construction at Gorgon is approximately 75 percent complete, and construction at Wheatstone is approximately 25 percent complete. Over the next four years we anticipate 15 project startups with a Chevron investment of more than $1 billion each, including two key deepwater projects in the U.S. Gulf of Mexico Jack/St. Malo and Big Foot, which are expected to come online in 2014 and 2015, respectively. </P>

<P>We continued to add resources to our portfolio through both exploration and targeted acquisitions in 2013. The success rate of our exploration wells was nearly 59 percent, and we added crude oil and natural gas resources through discoveries in 10 countries. We grew our portfolio of opportunities with a new operating interest in the Kurdistan Region of Iraq, new acreage in the Bight Basin offshore South Australia, and finalized agreements to pursue unconventional resources in Argentina as well as assume full operatorship of the Kitimat LNG plant and Pacific Trail Pipeline in Canada. We also successfully completed the first phase of our Duvernay Shale program in Canada. We added approximately 800 million barrels of net oil equivalent proved reserves, replacing almost 85 percent of production in 2013. The company’s three-year average reserve replacement ratio is 123 percent of net oil equivalent production. </P>
<Figure>
<ImageData src="images/Chevron 2013 Annual Report_img_12.jpg"/>
</Figure>
<Sect><Figure>

<ImageData src="images/Chevron 2013 Annual Report_img_14.jpg"/>
thesupporting local businesses. Beyond direct business investment and taxes, over the past eight years we contributed almost $1.5 billion to local communities through social investments that foster economic growth, with a signiﬁcant focus on health, education and economic development programs. You can ﬁnd more information in our 2013 Corporate Responsibility Report. The men and women of Chevron </Figure>
<Figure>

<ImageData src="images/Chevron 2013 Annual Report_img_15.jpg"/>
and invest in programs to create measurable and lasting value. Our business and social investments boost local economies by creating jobs, improving livelihoods and </Figure>
</Sect>
</Sect>
</Part>
</TaggedPDF-doc>