<!-- Mapping Table version: 28-February-2003 -->
<TaggedPDF-doc>
<?xpacket begin='<feff>' id='W5M0MpCehiHzreSzNTczkc9d'?>
<?xpacket begin="<feff>" id="W5M0MpCehiHzreSzNTczkc9d"?>
<x:xmpmeta xmlns:x="adobe:ns:meta/" x:xmptk="Adobe XMP Core 5.4-c005 78.147326, 2012/08/23-13:03:03        ">
   <rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">
      <rdf:Description rdf:about=""
            xmlns:xmp="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/"
            xmlns:pdf="http://ns.adobe.com/pdf/1.3/"
            xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
            xmlns:xmpMM="http://ns.adobe.com/xap/1.0/mm/">
         <xmp:CreateDate>2013-11-22T17:43Z</xmp:CreateDate>
         <xmp:ModifyDate>2014-06-29T07:30:51-07:00</xmp:ModifyDate>
         <xmp:MetadataDate>2014-06-29T07:30:51-07:00</xmp:MetadataDate>
         <pdf:Producer>WebFilings</pdf:Producer>
         <dc:format>xml</dc:format>
         <dc:title>
            <rdf:Alt>
               <rdf:li xml:lang="x-default">FY2013_Q4_10K</rdf:li>
            </rdf:Alt>
         </dc:title>
         <xmpMM:DocumentID>uuid:560cc65c-1227-4a1e-96ca-d52bbbdc43c2</xmpMM:DocumentID>
         <xmpMM:InstanceID>uuid:4c0bece0-4a44-4602-8d59-88f51498185f</xmpMM:InstanceID>
      </rdf:Description>
   </rdf:RDF>
</x:xmpmeta>
<?xpacket end="w"?>
<?xpacket end='r'?>
<bookmark-tree>
<bookmark title="Cover">
<destination structID="LinkTarget_510"/>
</bookmark>
</bookmark-tree>
<Figure>
<ImageData src="images/Annual Report Disney 2013_img_2.jpg"/>
</Figure>

<P>Dear Shareholders, January 2014 </P>

<P>Looking back at everything we’ve accomplished this year, I am once again awed by the tremendous creativity and commitment of the men and women who make up The Walt Disney Company. As always, our thousands of cast members and employees around the world continued to go beyond the expected to achieve the extraordinary for our consumers, our guests, and our shareholders. And I can think of no better way to start this letter highlighting our success than by expressing my profound and continued appreciation for the people who made it possible. With such immense talent and dedication going for us, there really is no limit to what we can achieve. </P>

<P>In the last several years we’ve effectively integrated the major acquisitions of Pixar and Marvel and are well on the way to doing the same with Lucasfilm, creating an unprecedented and unparalleled collection of the world’s greatest brands and creative content, along with tremendous growth potential for the foreseeable future. We’ve also made a number of strategic investments to position the company to create even greater value and leveraged the strength of our entire portfolio of businesses to grow our presence around the world. In the process, The Walt Disney Company has been recognized as one of the world’s most reputable, admired and socially responsible companies by the likes of Forbes, Fortune, and Barron’s – applauded for our overall performance as well as the integrity with which we operate. </P>

<Sect>
<H5>THE WALT DISNEY COMPANY AND SUBSIDIARIES
TABLE OF CONTENTS
</H5>

<P>The Walt Disney Company is doing really well.</P>
</Sect>

<Sect>
<H5>PART I </H5>

<P>Business 1 Risk Factors 17 Unresolved Staff Comments 22 Properties 23 Legal Proceedings 24 Mine Safety Disclosures 24 </P>

<P>Executive Officers of the Company 24 </P>
</Sect>

<Sect>
<H5>PART II </H5>

<P>ITEM 5. Market for the Company’s Common Equity, Related Stockholder Matters and Issuer Purchases of Equity </P>

<P>Securities 25 ITEM 6. Selected Financial Data 26 ITEM 7. Management’s Discussion and Analysis of Financial Condition and Results of Operations 27 ITEM 7A. Quantitative and Qualitative Disclosures About Market Risk 53 ITEM 8. Financial Statements and Supplementary Data 54 ITEM 9. Changes in and Disagreements with Accountants on Accounting and Financial Disclosure 54 ITEM 9A. Controls and Procedures 54 ITEM 9B. Other Information 54 </P>
</Sect>
</TaggedPDF-doc>
